How the East was won.
The Cowboy Way is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Gregg Champion.
Two championship rodeo partners travel to New York to find their
missing friend, Nacho Salazar who went missing there.
Pepper Lewis, played by Woody Harrelson.
Sonny Gilstrap, played by Kiefer Sutherland.
John Stark, played by Dylan McDermott.
Officer Sam 'Mad Dog' Shaw, played by Ernie Hudson.
Margarette, played by Marg Helgenberger.
Chango, played by Luis Guzmán.
The Cowboy Way is a 1994 American action comedy western film directed by Gregg
Champion and starring Woody Harrelson and Kiefer Sutherland.
The film explores themes of new york city, rodeo,
outlaw, modern west, buddy comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and intense.